Maker Collection of the UConn Marching Band 2009.0067
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
Maker Collection of the UConn Marching Band
undated, 1969-1983
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
2009.0067
2.75 Linear Feet
The collection contains musical scores arranged and drills designed for the University of Connecticut Marching Band by David Maker.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged topically. Musical arrangements have been arranged alphabetically by first letter of the title.
Series I: Inventory (undated, 1969-1983)
Scope and Contents
The collection contains musical scores arranged and drills designed for the University of Connecticut Marching Band by David Maker.
Connecticut (state); Storrs (inhabited place); Scores; Design drawings; Correspondence; Marching bands; University of Connecticut. Marching Band
- Series I: Drill Designs, 1969-1983
  - Other Drill Designs (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1969 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1970 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs 1970 Tour (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1971 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1972 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1973 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs 1974 Tour (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1974 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1975 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1976 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1977 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs 1978 Tour (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1978 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1979 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1980 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1970 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1981 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1981 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs 1981 Tour (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1982 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1982 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1983 (Box 1)
  - Drill Designs Fall 1983 (Box 1)